[
    {
        "front": "かんたん\n「な」",
        "back": "easy, simple",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちかい",
        "back": "near",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "とおい",
        "back": "far",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "はやい",
        "back": "fast, early",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "おそい",
        "back": "slow, late",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "おおい\n「ひとが～」",
        "back": "many[people] much",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "すくない\n「ひとが～」",
        "back": "few[people], a little",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "あたたかい",
        "back": "warm",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "すずしい",
        "back": "cool",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "あまい",
        "back": "sweet",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "からい",
        "back": "hot (taste), spicy",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "おもい",
        "back": "heavy",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "かるい",
        "back": "light",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "いい\n「コーヒーが」",
        "back": "prefer (coffee is good)",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "きせつ",
        "back": "season",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "はる",
        "back": "spring",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "なつ",
        "back": "summer",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "あき",
        "back": "autumn",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふゆ",
        "back": "winter",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "てんき",
        "back": "weather",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "あめ",
        "back": "rain, rainy",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆき",
        "back": "snow, snowy",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "くもり",
        "back": "cloudy",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "ホテル",
        "back": "hotel",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "くうこう",
        "back": "airport",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "うみ",
        "back": "sea, ocean",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "せかい",
        "back": "world",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "パーティー",
        "back": "party",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "(～おします ：give me a party)\n「お」まつり",
        "back": "festival",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "しけん",
        "back": "exam",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "すきやき",
        "back": "sukiyaki (beef and vegetable hot pot)",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "さしみ",
        "back": "sashimi (sliced raw fish)",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "「お」すし",
        "back": "Sushi (raw fish with vinegared rice dumplings)",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "てんぷら",
        "back": "tempura (seafood and vegetable deep fried)",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "いけばな\n(～おします ：practice flower arrangement)",
        "back": "flower arrangement",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "もみじ",
        "back": "maple, red leaves of autumn",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "どちら",
        "back": "which one (between two things)",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "どちらも",
        "back": "both",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "ずっと",
        "back": "by far",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "はじめて",
        "back": "for the first time",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "ただいま",
        "back": "I am home",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "おかえりなさい",
        "back": "welcome home",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "すごいですね",
        "back": "that’s amazing",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "でも",
        "back": "but",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "つかれました",
        "back": "(I’m) tired",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "よい",
        "back": "Good (formal)\n<i-adj.>",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "ヨーロッパ",
        "back": "Europe",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "れいぞうこ",
        "back": "Refrigerator",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほんや",
        "back": "Bookstore",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "としょかん・ としょしつ",
        "back": "Library",
        "chapter": "N5 C12"
    }
]